import { Question } from "../contestantControls";

export const benGQuestions: Question[] = [
  {
    id: 181,
    question: "What was the total prize pool of the Season 1 World Championship?",
    options: ["$20K", "$100K", "$50K"],
    correctAnswer: 1
  },
  {
    id: 182,
    question: "Which team won the Season 2 World Championship?",
    options: ["Abzu Frost", "Taipei Assassins", "Team WE"],
    correctAnswer: 1
  },
  {
    id: 183,
    question: "What is Faker’s full name?",
    options: ["Lee Sang-hyeok", "Jeong Ji-hoon", "Choi Woo-je"],
    correctAnswer: 0
  },
  {
    id: 184,
    question: "Which Korean team went undefeated at Worlds 2015 until the Finals?",
    options: ["EDG", "KOO", "SKT"],
    correctAnswer: 1
  },
  {
    id: 185,
    question: "Which team won the first-ever MSI in 2015?",
    options: ["SKT", "EDG", "KOO"],
    correctAnswer: 2
  },
  {
    id: 186,
    question: "At which Worlds did Riot first introduce the 'Pick and Ban Music' we still hear today?",
    options: ["2011", "2013", "2012"],
    correctAnswer: 1
  },
  {
    id: 187,
    question: "Which team won Worlds 2020?",
    options: ["DAMWON", "G2", "JDG"],
    correctAnswer: 0
  },
  {
    id: 188,
    question: "Which NA team made the Finals of MSI 2016?",
    options: ["TL", "CLG", "C9"],
    correctAnswer: 1
  },
  {
    id: 189,
    question: "Who was the first LEC player to reach 10 domestic titles?",
    options: ["Caps", "Jankos", "Rekkles"],
    correctAnswer: 2
  },
  {
    id: 190,
    question: "Which LPL team is known as 'The People’s Team' in China?",
    options: ["RNG", "BLG", "WBG"],
    correctAnswer: 0
  },
  {
    id: 191,
    question: "Which team won MSI 2023?",
    options: ["JDG", "T1", "RNG"],
    correctAnswer: 0
  },
  {
    id: 192,
    question: "Which champion has had the most appearances in LoL world’s tournaments?",
    options: ["Gragas", "Corki", "Lee Sin"],
    correctAnswer: 2
  },
  {
    id: 193,
    question: "Which champion had the highest Pick/Ban rate on the World’s main stage in 2023?",
    options: ["Orianna", "Xayah", "Jarvan IV"],
    correctAnswer: 0
  },
  {
    id: 194,
    question: "What is the record for highest farm in a LoL pro game?",
    options: ["1143", "1465", "975"],
    correctAnswer: 1
  },
  {
    id: 195,
    question: "Which champion had the highest Pick/Ban rate on the World’s main stage in 2024?",
    options: ["Aurora", "Yone", "Skarner"],
    correctAnswer: 1
  }
];